Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
Rescue against Fate
Episode 52
You should go now.
Green.
Paddi.
Paddi, Paddi.
Come quick! Paddi is here.
Paddi, are you okay?
Everyone, Green really did let you go.
What happened here?
Blue merged everyone together.
What exactly is he trying to achieve by merging everyone?
He also took the Absorption Device.
It must be to carry out his original plan.
Original plan?
Could it be…
We have to stop him immediately.
Weslie, wait for us!
Hold on.
My drones will bring Weslie back.
You guys, follow me back to Green Green Grassland right away.
We must prepare for the worst.
Mr. Slowy…
Mr. Slowy, we can use Peach’s World Teleportation Device to get back.
Weslie
Don’t even think about absorbing other worlds.
What are you going to stop me with? That ridiculous sticker of yours?
If I could stop you once, I can stop you a second time.
Don’t talk big.
Only the weak mistake luck for skill.
Stop looking down on me.
You won’t get lucky again.
This is…
This is the Absorption Device you guys destroyed.
Watch me destroy it again and stop you from doing any more evil.
You’ve wasted too much of my time.
Let the great absorption plan begin now.
The Absorption Device has merged with me now; let’s see how you destroy it.
Ketian
Stop lazing in bed.
It’s time to go stand guard.
Hurry up.
The world won’t end if I skip guard duty for a day.
What are you doing? Pulling at my blanket?
It wasn’t me.
I just wanted to sleep in; surely that won’t cause the end of the world.
—Brother! —Brother!
Help!
What’s going on here?
I don’t know. Let’s save them first.
It’s finally sprouting!
Everyone, let’s hurry to the shelter.
What is happening? Is this the end of the world?
We need to activate the Protective Dome immediately.
Use Peach’s device to return to Green Green Grassland.
It’s safer than trying to force our way through the rift.
Mr. Slowy, what you just said
about “preparing for the worst”—what did you mean by that?
Here.
This is…
This is a device to prevent energy conversion.
In the event that the Absorption Device ends up in Blue’s hands,
this device might help you avert disaster.
Blue has the Absorption Device now; regardless of whether Weslie can stop him,
we need to get back to Green Green Grassland as soon as possible to protect the others.
That’s right—Wolnie and Wilie are still back at Green Green Grassland.
Peach even foresaw this; I think she’s even more amazing than Mr. Slowy.
Said who? We are on the same level!
She even invented the World Teleportation Device.
Peach really is more capable.
What’s happening to this world?
Oh no.
The Protective Dome of Goats’ Village isn’t working.
Quick, we need to bring the other survivors here for shelter.
We only managed to bring back so few people…
I…I’m just so useless.
No, you’ve done a great job.
Leave the rest to me.
Planie.
Goats’ Village has made it this far thanks to you.
That’s right, Planie is amazing.
Thank you all.
If we just channel the power from the Energization Prevention Device into the Goats’ Village Protective Dome,
the Dome will be reinforced.
It worked.
Where’s Wolffy? Didn’t he come back with us?
Where did he go?
He went to pick up Wolnie and Wilie.
Why is the sky splitting open?
Mommy, are we going to get sucked in too?
No, don’t be afraid; Mommy is here.
Wilie
Mommy
Great! Daddy is here to save me.
Wolffy, you’re finally back.
Now isn’t the time for reminiscing.
We’d better take the drone to Goats’ Village for shelter.
Hold tight—we’re taking off.
Maybe I should pilot instead.
That works too.
Why is the suction getting stronger the closer we get to Goats’ Village?
Don’t worry about piloting, Wolnie.
I’ll keep you both safe.
Daddy is amazing!
It’s Wolffy family—quick, open the door and let them in.
Finally, safe.
Wolnie, are you guys okay?
I’ll take you to rest.
We’re fine.
Is Weslie back?
Don’t worry, he’s fine.
I’ll go find him.
Let’s go save the others.
Why are there more and more rifts?
Don’t worry; I’ll definitely get you to safety.
It’s Queen Nuan and Lan Zhuzhu.
Everyone is mostly safe now; let’s find a place to take cover.
Sister Xi’er.
Xiao Mei.
Xi Huahua.
It’s all my fault—I failed to grab Queen Nuan.
Let’s not talk about that right now.
More and more people are being sucked away.
We have to save them.
But the suction force out there is so strong—how can we save them?
I have a plan.
Based on my observations and analysis,
the energy sphere sucks in energy molecules in a clockwise spiral pattern.
As long as our bodies haven’t been energized yet,
we can rescue the people near Green Green Grassland.
But wouldn’t we get energized the moment we step outside?
Don’t worry; I’ve combined the Energization Prevention Device Peach gave me with these raincoats.
Once you put them on, you’ll be able to temporarily resist the suction,
and won’t get energized.
We can’t see it once the raincoat is on.
Mr. Slowy, you’re playing favorites! My raincoat is so small.
Weslie’s is so big.
Weslie has wings, after all, so it naturally needs to be a bit bigger.
How come I don’t have a raincoat?
Your stuffing is showing through your backside; leave the rescue work to us.
Wolffy, let me help you patch up your body.
They’re too spread out; let’s split up to rescue them.
Okay.
Why does he look so much like me?
Weslie
We’re safe now.
Don’t be afraid.
Don’t hold on so tight.
—Sister Xi’er! —Danger!
I’ll go save Xi’er.
You guys take them back first.
Don’t worry, Weslie will definitely save Sister Xi’er.
That’s right—trust Weslie.
To be continued